This area here, between the eyebrows, is a zone that indicates when someone truly
この眉間の部分は、誰かが本当に苦しんでいるときに示す領域です。
is experiencing suffering,
苦しんでいるとき、
or going through suffering in their life, whether it be physical, emotional, or otherwise,
それが肉体的、感情的、その他の苦しみであろうと、人生で苦しみを経験しているとき、
you will observe this here, and in the eyes as well; you can perceive the eye almost making a movement, like this.
あなたはここにそれを見るでしょう。そして目にも、ほら、目がほとんどこのように動いているのがわかるでしょう。
There is a specific geometry within the iris that can manifest in this manner, which...
虹彩には、このように現れる幾何学模様があり、それは...
It is also an initiation point that is also related
これはまた、関連する開始点でもあります。
with the...
...
The brain's primordium, at the outset, is flat.
脳の欠陥は、最初は平らです。
And through the process of telencephalization, it undergoes this transformation.
そして、遠隔脳化のプロセスによって、それはこうなります。
This is where the crista galli is established.
ここに鶏冠が形成されます。
It is a point of concentration.
これは集中点です。
We call it the eye of clairvoyance.
私たちはこれを透視の目と呼びます。
You have 'voyance'.
あなたには透視能力があります。
In this instance, one utilizes the other's emotions.
ここでは、他者の感情を利用します。
I will interact with your astral plane.
私はあなたのアストラルプレーンで遊びます。
And then, you have clairvoyance.
そして、あなたには透視能力があります。
That is to say, you begin to perceive the world entirely.
つまり、あなたは世界を完全に別の視点から見始めるということです。
from the perspective of the other. This implies perceiving their operational mechanisms. This, in itself, constitutes a form of clairvoyance.
他者の。それは、あなたが彼がどのように機能するかを見ることを意味します。これはすでに透視です。
This occurs here. And then, you have the third and unique form of 'voyance', which is polyvoyance.
これはここで行われます。そして、3番目で唯一の透視能力、それが多視です。
You
あなたは
begin to perceive God or this divinity in everything. You have
すべてのものの中に神、あるいはこの神性を見始めるでしょう。あなたには
an electromagnetic spectrum.
電磁スペクトルがあります。
This is what is perceived. You see, if I have developed, in fact, it
これが私たちが見ているものです。ほら、もし私が成長したなら、実際、それは
is already quite significant. It is our rainbow
すでにかなり良いです。それは私たちの虹です。
of light.
光の。
However, observe what this represents as reality, you see, surrounding us.
しかし、それが私たちの周りの現実として何を表しているかを見てください。
All that exists, all these frequencies; the more one enhances their capacities,
そこにあるすべてのもの、これらのすべての周波数、能力を少し高めれば高めるほど、
one can sometimes perceive phenomena slightly beyond the ordinary.
時には少し変わったものを見ることができます。
The eye will receive luminous information; thus, it will receive a photon.
目は光の情報を受け取るので、光子を受け取ります。
The very first layer that will be traversed will be the conjunctiva.
最初に通過する層は結膜です。
The second layer to be traversed will be the cornea.
2番目に通過する層は角膜です。
The cornea, which is the anterior portion...
角膜は...
...of the sclera, transparent.
前方の強膜の透明な部分です。
Then, you will have the passage through the pupil.
次に、瞳孔のレベルで通過します。
So, the first chamber anteriorly is the anterior chamber,
したがって、前方の最初の部屋は前房です。
which contains aqueous humor.
そこには房水が含まれています。
The anterior chamber, the iris, with the pupil here, which
前房、虹彩、そしてここには瞳孔が
allows passage.
通っています。
And here, you have a so-called posterior chamber,
そして、ここには後房と呼ばれる部屋があります。
which still contains the same fluid.
そこには常に同じ液体が含まれています。
But anteriorly here, you have what are called the ciliary bodies,
しかし、ここには毛様体と呼ばれるものがあります。
which also produce [fluid].
それもまた作られます。
fluid, and slightly posterior here to what is called the limbus, you will find
液体と、ここにある輪部と呼ばれるものの少し後ろには、
the canal
管があります。
of Schlemm, or scleral venous sinus, which reabsorbs [fluid]. So, there
シュレム管または強膜管は再吸収されるので、
is continuously a fluid that
常に液体が
circulates here, which sustains and nourishes. Then it will traverse and encounter what is
ここで循環し、生き、栄養を与え、それが通過し、
called the crystalline lens, responsible for accommodation. And at the level of the crystalline lens, the vitreous humor
水晶体と呼ばれるものと出会います。
traverses to
水晶体では、硝子体が
reach my
通過して、
retina, which is composed of different layers. So, not only do I perceive only a small light spectrum, but I am still capable of detecting the smallest possible quantity of light, called a photon. Furthermore, I have a constricted field of vision.
私の網膜に到達します。
I have a
網膜は異なる層でできています。ですから、私は小さな光スペクトルしか捉えませんが、
possible vision, which is a centered vision, and I also have a very interesting vision, which is peripheral vision. I must learn to utilize these two types of vision. Thus, a frequency,
それでも可能な限り最小の光量、つまり光子を捉えることができます。さらに、視野が狭まっています。
a wave.
私は可能な限り最小の光量、つまり光子を捉えることができます。さらに、視野が狭まっています。
and a spectrum that, at maximum, varies in a foveal field of
私は
5 degrees,
中心視という可能な視覚を持っており、また非常に興味深い視覚、
c'est la vision périphérique. Je dois apprendre à utiliser ces deux visions. Donc une fréquence,
つまり周辺視も持っています。これら2つの視覚を使いこなすことを学ぶ必要があります。つまり、周波数、
une onde.
波です。
et  un  spectre  qui,  maximum,  varie  en  fétrade  de
そして、最大で5度の範囲で変化するスペクトルです。
5  degrés,
5度です。
in fact, even regarding 23 degrees, but I will explain that a bit later.
実際には23度ですが、それは後で説明します。
It is a 23-degree angle, like the orientation of your heart,
それはあなたの心臓の向きと同じ23度です。
like the orientation of the Earth, like the orientation of your inner ears.
地球の向きと同じ、内耳の向きと同じです。
There are specific angulations within the body.
体には特定の角度があります。
This will reach the retina, initiating what is known as the phenomenon of transduction,
それは網膜に行き、変換現象と呼ばれるものを行います。
converting photons into electrical signals.
この光子のレベルを電気に変換します。
into a nervous impulse that will be transmitted to
神経の流れに変換され、それが
the left and to the right,
左右に伝達されます。
for each eye, at the level of what is referred to as the LGN,
各眼ごとに、CGEと呼ばれるもの、
i.e., the lateral geniculate nucleus,
つまり外側膝状体で、
which will provide an interpretation, demonstrating how it integrates this information,
それがこの情報をどのように統合するかという解釈を与えます。
parvocellular, koniocellular, magnocellular,
小細胞性、大細胞性、巨細胞性、
which represent specific types of information.
これらは特定の情報となります。
Subsequently, once this process is complete...
そして、それが終わると、
It will then utilize what are known as the optic radiations to project towards the
それは視放線と呼ばれるものを取り、
visual cortex, specifically above and below the calcarine fissure.
視覚野、つまり鳥距溝の上下に向かいます。
This is very interesting and crucial to be able to localize.
非常に興味深く、位置を特定することが非常に重要です。
This renowned journey, from the eye, encompassing all the interpretation we observe here,
この有名な旅、眼、ここに見られるすべての解釈、
and these radiations projecting towards these cortical areas and towards the various
そしてこれらの放射線は、これらの皮質領域と異なる
levels of interpretation.
解釈のレベルに向かいます。
which we will now examine in a bit more detail.
これから少し詳しく見ていきましょう。